Guide to the Stanford University, Office of Undergraduate Admissions, Records
Stanford University. Libraries.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford University, Office of Undergraduate Admissions, records
1962-1985
SC0407
Stanford University. Office of Undergraduate Admissions.
18.5 Linear feet
General office files containing correspondence, memoranda, policies, surveys, reports, speeches, minutes, articles, and other records pertaining to policies and procedures, academic planning, housing, recruitment, financial aid, legislation, and other issues. Persons represented in the files include deans Fred A. Hargadon and Jean H. Fetter; assistant provost Raymond F. Bacchetti; and G. Robert Hamrdla of the undergraduate studies office.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives Green Library 557 Escondido Mall Stanford, CA 94305-6064 Email: specialcollections@stanford.edu Phone: (650) 725-1022 URL: http://library.stanford.edu/spc
Administrative Information
Provenance
Administrative transfer, 1987.
Information about Access
Restricted: for more information, contact the University Archivist.
Description of the Collection
General office files containing correspondence, memoranda, policies, surveys, reports, speeches, minutes, articles, and other records pertaining to policies and procedures, academic planning, housing, recruitment, financial aid, legislation, and other issues. Persons represented in the files include deans Fred A. Hargadon and Jean H. Fetter; assistant provost Raymond F. Bacchetti; and G. Robert Hamrdla of the undergraduate studies office.
Access Terms
Bacchetti, Raymond F., 1934-; Fetter, Jean H.; Hamrdla, G. Robert.; Stanford University. Office of Undergraduate Admissions.; Universities and colleges--Admission.
Collection Contents
- Records
  - Donald Kennedy memos, January 21, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - President Lyman correspondence, 1971-79 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Speeches - Richard Lyman, 1973-77 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Jean Fetter memo re: alumni children and admissions, Dec. 13, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Fred Glover re: Linda Clever memo on newspaper articles, May 4, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Bob Hamrdla - article from METAS, publication of Aspira of American, Inc., Sept. 24, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Memos from assistants to the President - Stone, Nogales, Simmons, Shaw, 1972-74 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Robert R. Ausburger - VP for business and financial, August 1975 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Bienenstock News Reports, 1975-76 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - IRS admissions policies - business & financial services, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - University relations - Melinda Howe memos, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Provost's Office - Keith Smith - Personnel reqs., July 14, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Al Hastorf-Acting Provost memo re: self-evaluation survey: programs for physically limited, Feb. 5, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - William Massey - Vice Provost memos, 1974-77 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - William Miller - Vice President & Provost, 1971-78 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Ray Bacchetti - Vice Provost memos, 197-78 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Budget Adjustment Program - remarks by R. Bacchetti at Student Talk Series, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Transfer credit - Ray Bacchetti, 1972-73 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Center for Interdisciplinary Research - Massey, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Edward E. Shaw - Assoc. Provost memos, 1971-78 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - E.E. Shaw - Academic Goal, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Ombudsman - proposal for, May, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - AIC - Bob Hamrdla, 1972-76 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - AIC, 1978-79 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - AIC - senior survey, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - AIC -Survey of future academic plans of graduating students - class of 1974 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Survey of future academic plans for graduating students - class of 1973 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - "The Senior Survey 1975" (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Senior survey, 1971-72 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Pre-meds at Stanford - Prof. S.A. Rosenberg, 1981-86 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Academic planning, 1976-77 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - - survey A/NC analysis, 1974-75 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - reports, 1972-73 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - research II, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - , 1971 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - NCHEMS guide to data resources, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - James Lyons, Dean of Student Affairs, 4/73-9/85 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Student affairs - DOSA - annual report, 1973-74 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - On campus student employment policies - Dean of Student's Office, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Larry Horton - Assoc. Dean of Student Affairs, 8-9/76 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Survey of commuting students at Stanford, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Housing - Student Affairs Office, 1972-74 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Room and board rates, March 22, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Study of residential life, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Summer session, Feb. 11, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - David Fulton - development office, 1978 and 1985 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - George T. Gregory - legal - GSO, Aug. 26, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - GSO general correspondence, 1977 and 1979 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Gift program, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - University progress fund, June 28. 1971 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Alumni Association, 1972 and 1976 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Non-matriculated students - Tom Rhue, Asst. Dean of Graduate Studies, May 30, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Review of Graduate Division, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Stanford Daily - JHF interview questions by Charlie Gofen, May 4, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Stanford admissions seminar in LA area, Spring 1975 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Alumni admissions seminar - LA, May 1974 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Introduce Pres. Lyman, freshman orientation program, Sept. 26, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Academy Arts & Sciences university governance meeting (NYC), June 19, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Admissions & Guidance Institute, July 18, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Bishop school address, Fall 1969 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - CERAS conference for education writers, Jan. 20, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Eastern alumni meetings, Sept. 8-18, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Fund raisers talk, 4/15/77 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Harvard summer institute, July 25, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Seminar for administrators for Japanese private universities, Sept. 10, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Journalism fellows seminar, Oct. 27, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Speech - Katharine Branson Chapter - the cum laude society, Jan. 8, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Menlo School Mothers Club, Menlo School, May 11, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - NACAC conference workshop, Feb. 21, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - NACAC - Chicago - equal opportunity & academic freedom, June 30, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Parent's league speech (The Search for a College), ca. 1971 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Sierra Camp (FAH as guest speaker), July 20-27, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Simulated admissions process - Sierra camp, July 1971 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - U.C. Irvine meeting, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Volunteer conference, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Swarthmore-talks on admissions to alumni, etc., 1968 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - The Recruitment Function at Stanford - report to C-UAFA, June 1976 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - For distribution from FAH - memos on various subjects, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Reports & Surveys
    - Admissions data - general, March 1973 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - "Survey of Athletes" by Undergraduate Studies, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Report of the University Comm. on Athletics and Physical Education, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Report: faculty self-discipline, Jan. 1971 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Professor McDonald - GSB - faculty tenure, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Freshmen applications to four-year institutions (3/1/72 & one year earlier)-survey by CEEB, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Harvard minority overlap study, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Harvard overlap college admissions study, 1966-69 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Report on the influence of financial aid factors on freshman enrollment...by Conway, Verducci, Hopkins, Massey, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - Jasper Ridge biological preserve - a unviersity policy statement submitted by Bio Sci (copy), August 1974 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Thomas C. Moser, English Dept. - jobs for Ph.D's, October 15, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - Lewis, John - Report on sabbatical year, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - Survey of off-campus students - housing, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - PROJECT INFO - progress report, April 1972 (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - Report on financing alternative for public events - Tam Bacchetti, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - Report of the Ad Hoc Committee on Residential Education, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - Student housing needs at Stanford, Jan. 1979 (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - Student traits: survey (Saunders), 1958 (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - Summary of degrees granted, 1975-76 (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - Task force on tenure/teaching quality, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Legislation
    - Legislation to watch, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 45)
    - SB 2005 Truth in Testing, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 46)
    - H.R. 10076-"Omnibus Right to Privacy Act," 1977 (Box 2, Folder 47)
    - Guidelines to Buckley Amendment, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 48)
    - HR69 - "Rights and Privacy" Amendment to Higher Education Bill - Buckley, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - O'Hara bill - HR3471 - to amend title IV of higher education act of 1965, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - HEW Title IX of Ed. amendment-proposed regulations, 1974-75 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - California fair employment practice act, May, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Cross lawsuit, 1971 and 1973 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Courts and universities - Supreme Court ruling, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Higher education act (Effective July 1972), Sept. 15, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - AB 3862 & AB 1770, 1974 and 1973 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Rehabilitation act 1973 - 504 nondiscrimination on basis of handicap, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Legal advisor to the president, James V. Siena, Jan. 28, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Privacy - Student Records - Lists - Etc.
    - Principles of privacy in university, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Report of the Ad Hoc Committee on Protection of Privacy of Information at Stanford, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Privacy and student records, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Rights & Responsibilities
    - "Rights & Responsibilities" - sent to incoming freshmen, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Regulations governing student conduct & procedures for their enforcement, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Grading practices, March 11, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - McClenahan, June 17, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Kenneth S. Pitzer memo on safety of S.U. buildings, May 4, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Chicano Asst. Directors, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Ray Bacchetti memo & cc of Earlham College letter, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Helen Kmetovic - Transfer suggestions (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Richard Lyman, acting president memos, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Rick Turner, Asst. Director, UAO memos, 1970-71 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - John Lewis, special associate letter, Sept. 17, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Frannie Robinson (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Howard Brooks, vice provost memos, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - B.Y.U. correspondence, 1969-70 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Former personnel, 1969-70 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Recommendations, 1969-70 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Gil Chavez, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Caroline Audrich, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - Douglas Walker - student visiting program, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - NATIONAL NORMS FOR ENTERING COLLEGE FRESHMEN-FALL 1968, Dec. 3, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Student-alumni associates & their addresses, Nov. 1969 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - Hoglund recruitment program, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - Student visitor responses, Sept. 25, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - Upward Bound Program, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - Task Force Students admitted 1970 (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - B-M-A Indian (minority admission), 1969-70 (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - Alumni Association memos & correspondence, 1968-70 (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - 1967-68 freshman prediction formula, based on two-year experience, 1965-66, 1966-67 (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - Overseas studies, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - ASSU oversears studies task force, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 43)
    - Presidential commission on overseas campuses, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 44)
    - Overseas campuses Observer article, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 45)
    - Public affairs, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 46)
    - Registrar - Sally Mahoney, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 47)
    - Grading - Stanford - Mahoney, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 48)
    - Student service system, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 49)
    - Registrar - search, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 50)
    - Katchadourian, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 51)
    - Commission on Undergraduate Studies, 1979-80 (Box 3, Folder 52)
    - James Gibbs, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 53)
    - Undergraduate studies report, 1970-72 (Box 3, Folder 54)
    - A Stanford Education, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 55)
    - Robert Freelen, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 56)
    - Admission commission discussion topics, 1970-71 (Box 3, Folder 57)
    - MacKinnon speech, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 58)
    - Admission Commission - documents, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 59)
    - - correspondence, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 60)
    - - Financial Aid, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 61)
    - Admission Commission - minutes, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - - makeup, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Quad statement, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - ACT/SAT tables, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Bates college case, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Transfer admission, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Enrollment projections, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - ACT, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Data processing - admissions, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Coding sheets, 1970-71 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Admissions - general correspondence, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Affidavits - Cross case, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Admissions - Faculty - Staff children (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - "A" letter program - letter to alumni, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Black admission - transfer, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Asian/American, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Tuition, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Room and board, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - National achievement scholars, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - SES: admissions, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Open admissions - lottery, etc. (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Tuition/grant eligibility, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Application fees, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Fee waiver: CEEB guidelines, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Memo: revision app. forms and process, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Independent schools letter, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - California state scholarships, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - National Merit scholars - freshman, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Jack Black: accept/decline study, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Alumni schools comm., 1970 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Egad statement, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - APO report, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Trustees '85 (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - CA State Dept. Ed. Prof. Exam. Matters, 5/11/82 (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - Computer application - functional description Stanford student data base system, October 1976 (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - Rebuttal to Stanford Daily articles by Fred A. Hargadon, 1971-77 (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - Stanford University news service, 1973-75 (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - , 1975-76 (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - Stanford University Medical Center News Bureau, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - Athletics, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Athletics 1.6 ruling ACT,SAT, etc, 1968-70 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Letters of Recommendation (Fred A. Hargadon), 1960-74 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Travel policies & procedures (FAH), 1970 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - FAH speech-Westlake school commencement, 6/7/72 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Stanford alumni admissions seminar, 5/8/76 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - ABC (A Better Chance, Inc.), 1978 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Loan reports, 1973-77 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Univ. student loan program (Larry Hough), 1973 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - AGFAP - CA student aid commission, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - - Fred A. Hargadon, 2/16/69 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - (Advisory Group on Financial Aid Problems), 3/30/68 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - CA student aid commission - San Diego, 1/11-12/78 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Agenda-joint meeting of Student Aid Commission Ad Hoc Committee on the Single Common Financial Aid Form & the Advisory Group on Financial Aid Problems, 1/11/78 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - CA student aid commission, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - AGFAP - CA student aid commission, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - (Marmaduke), 1977 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - CA student aid commission meeting, 6/7/76 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - College opportunity grant, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - program, 1974-75 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - advisory committee, June, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - program, 1970-73 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - program, 1969-70 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Public service internship program, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - National achievement scholarship program, 1976-78 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - for outstanding Negro students, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Mailing to finalists in national achievement scholarship program (Black), 1973-75 (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - National consortium for black professional dev., 1975 (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - National merit scholarship corp., 1972 (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Special scholarships: other colleges (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Youth opportunities foundation (Los Angeles), 1971 (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - The S&H foundation, inc., 1971-74 (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Stanford club scholarships, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - Advanced placement, 1975-77 (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Ad hoc panel on advanced placement, 1974-75 (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - Statewide advanced placement committee, 1969-71 (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - American college testing programs conversion table to SAT (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - TOEFL test of English as a foreign language (Box 5, Folder 38)
    - CLEP (Box 5, Folder 39)
    - Residence configuration, 1970-71 (Box 5, Folder 40)
    - Cluster - house residents, 1970-71 (Box 5, Folder 41)
    - Student residential study, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 42)
    - Gibbs' informal discussion group, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 43)
    - CYFA - make-up, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 44)
    - CFYA - agendas, 1970-71 (Box 5, Folder 45)
    - CFYA - minutes, 1970-71 (Box 5, Folder 46)
    - Freshman orientation committee, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 47)
    - CFYA - documents I, 1969-70 (Box 5, Folder 48)
    - CFYA - documents II, 1970-71 (Box 5, Folder 49)
    - Class registration - by departments, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Foreign students, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Summer school, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Foreign students - Stanford, 1969-70 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Student special service proposal, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Approaching Stanford, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Grading systems - college (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Co-ed dorms, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Freshman profiles - other colleges, 1965-69 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Minorities, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Stanford/Howard exchange, 1978-85 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Bowdoin, 1973, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Brown University, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - CA Institute of Technology, 1978, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - CA Universities & Colleges, 1972, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Claremont Men's College, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Cornell (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Harvard admissions (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - News articles - Harvard (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Univ. of CA policy/undergrad. adm. (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - National Task Force/Fund for Improvement of Postsecondary Education (HEW), 1976 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - CUAFA, 1974-76 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - - annual report, 1975-76 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Academic advising at Stanford report, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - University fellows, 1978-79 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - executive committee, 1975-76 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - COFHE, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - Admissions office survey, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - COFHE, 1976-78 (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - , 1974-75 (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - Application forms notes (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - Application forms - Swarthmore (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - Engineering, 1969-71 (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - Private schools - USA, 7/10/67 (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - Admissions questionnaire (accepted/not enrolled), 8/9/68 (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - Workshop (admissions - alumni) (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - Less time, more options: education beyond the high school, 12/1970 (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - Heritage fund '71 (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - ROTC/NROTC, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 39)
    - Alumni Council representative - Haverford College, 91/6/70 (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - WACAC list, 2/5/71 (Box 6, Folder 41)
    - "Done" - misc. programs (mostly thank-you notes), 1970 (Box 6, Folder 42)
    - Fred A. Hargadon talk - R. Lyman dinner, 3/9/71 (Box 6, Folder 43)
    - "A" candidate follow-up, 1962-68 (Box 6, Folder 44)
    - School visit reports, 1969-70 (Box 6, Folder 45)
    - Office procedure and policy, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 46)
    - College & univ. environment scales, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 47)
    - Student recruiters, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 48)
    - Ford Foundation meeting, 5/27/70 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - National Council of Teachers of English, 1/1975 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Letter to the Editor (Palo Alto Times), 5/10/70 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Time, 1/17/72 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Time - ltr to the ed. (Donham letters-women admissions), 3/20/72 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - "Testing" - news items & reports, 1972-73 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Articles: tests, 1970-72 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - : tuition, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - : higher education-tutoring, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - : women, 1970-71 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - : secondary education, 1971-73 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - : higher education, 1966-73 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - : higher education II, 1963-72 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Admissions film outakes, circa 1984-1985; Accession ARCH-2002-265
  - The Farm -- 4 Jocks/Historical Muybridge Photo/Carla, 1980s; 1 film reel(s) (16mm) (Box 1)
  - Miscellaneous Trimsm Trims- Fine Cut, 1980s; 1 film reel(s) (16mm) (Box 1)
  - Hunger Rally Ext., 1980s; 1 film reel(s) (16mm) (Box 1)
  - The Farm -- Hopkins Marine Station, 1980s; 1 film reel(s) (16mm) (Box 1)
  - Don Kennedy -- Frosh Advisee (Wild Sound), 1980s; 1 film reel(s) (16mm) (Box 1)
  - Mos Jasper Ridge + Ehrlich, 1980s; 1 film reel(s) (16mm) (Box 1)
  - B. Randolph Sync Interview Mos--Ext. house and class, 1980s; 1 film reel(s) (16mm) (Box 1)
  - Class, J. Adams, Viss Door, Mos, 1980s; 1 film reel(s) (16mm) (Box 1)
  - R. Helliwell Antartica Fine Cut Trims (1/2), 1980s; 1 film reel(s) (16mm) (Box 1)
  - R. Helliewll Antartica Fine Cut Trims (2/2), 1980s; 1 film reel(s) (16mm) (Box 1)
  - G. Harrison and Ensemble (Wild Sound) Takes 1-10, 1980s; 1 film reel(s) (16mm) (Box 2)
  - J. Gibbons, 1980s; 1 film reel(s) (16mm) (Box 2)
  - Painting Class (Not edge coded), 1980s; 1 film reel(s) (16mm) (Box 2)
  - Wild Sound -- Shinkman-Berstein -- VTSS- Middlebrook, 1980s; 1 film reel(s) (16mm) (Box 2)
  - Ted Kennedy, 1980s; 1 film reel(s) (16mm) (Box 2)
  - David Kennedy Sync, 1980s; 1 film reel(s) (16mm) (Box 2)
  - Stanford Band, 1980s; 1 film reel(s) (16mm) (Box 2)
  - D. Scott Take 1-3 also at Daily with K. Olmstead (Wild sound computer at Daily), 1980s; 1 film reel(s) (16mm) (Box 2)
  - D. Middlebrook, 1980s; 1 film reel(s) (16mm) (Box 2)
  - Kids at Boat House, Boathouse 2 (Rough Cut, Trims, Wild Sound, Outtakes), 1980s; 1 film reel(s) (16mm) (Box 2)
  - Admissions Office Take 1 CU Letters; Take 2 MS Letters; Take 3A,B,C Keith Light (Rough Cut), 1980s; 1 film reel(s) (16mm) (Box 3)